Finding aid for the Hearst Corporation Los Angeles Examiner photographs, negatives and clippings - oversize portrait and subject files 7000.3
USC Libraries Special Collections
- Oversize Portrait Files
  - L
    - Lockwood -- Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Lodge -- Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Lomakin, Jacob -- General (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Lombard, Carole (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Lombardo -- Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - London, Julie -- Actress (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Long -- Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Longden, Johnnie -- Jockey (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Lopez -- Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Lora-Loz (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Lord -- Miscellaneous (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Loring, Lorring -- Miscellaneous (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Louis, Joe -- Prize fighter (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Louis, Joe -- Versus Walcott -- Fight Pictures (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Louise, Anita (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Love -- Miscellaneous (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Love, Bessie -- Actress (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Lovejoy, Frank (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Lovett -- Miscellaneous (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Lovett, Robbie -- Mrs. -- Mother of Jay Lovett (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Lovett, Robert (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Lowe, Edmund -- Actor (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Loy, Myrna (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Lu-Ly (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Luce -- Miscellaneous (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Luckman -- Miscellaneous (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Luft, Sid (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Lukas -- Miscellaneous (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Luna, John -- Screen Actor (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Lundigan -- Miscellaneous (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Lundigan, William (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Lupino, Ida (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Lusk -- Miscellaneous (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Luther -- Miscellaneous (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Lynch -- Miscellaneous (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Lynn -- Miscellaneous (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Lynn, Diana -- Actress (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Lyon, Lyons -- Miscellaneous (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - M
    - Ma-Maf (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - MacArthur, Arthur -- Son of General (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - MacArthur, Douglas -- Alone (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - MacArthur, Douglas -- Groups (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - MacArthur, Douglas -- Life Magazine Story by Courtney Whitney (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, General (Box 120, Folder 2 - 3)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, General -- Aboard Plane (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, General -- Groups (Box 120, Folder 6-15)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, General -- Groups of Three (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, General -- Groups of Two (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, General -- Los .Angeles Visit January 1955 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, General -- Pictures Without Him (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - MacFadden, Bernarr (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Mack -- Miscellaneous (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Mack, Charles Emmett -- And Mrs. (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Mackall -- Miscellaneous (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - MacKaye, Dorothy -- Actress (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - MacLaine, Shirley (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - MacMurray, Fred (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - MacRae, Gordon (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Madison -- Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Madison, Guy -- Actor (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Mag-Mak (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Magnani, Anna -- Actress (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Magnuson, Warren, Senator (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Maguire, Mary -- Actress (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Main, Marjorie -- Actress (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Mal-Maq (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Malik, Jacob Alexander (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Mallory -- Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Malone -- Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Malone, Dorothy -- Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Mangrum, Lloyd -- Golf (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Manjou, Adolphe -- Actor (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Mann -- Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Manning -- Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Mansfeldt, Annie Irene -- And Husband Dr. John H. (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Mansfield, Jayne -- Actress (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Mantz -- Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Maples, Virginia -- Actress (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Mar-Marc (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Mara, Adele (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Maragon, John (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - March -- Miscellaneous (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Marciano, Rocky -- Boxer -- The Champ Now (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Mard-Marj (Box 116, Folder 5-6)
    - Markey, Gene (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Marley, Peverall -- Mr. and Mrs. -- Linda Darnell (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Marlowe, Hugh (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Marsh -- Miscellaneous (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Marshall -- Miscellaneous (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Marshall, Brenda -- Actress (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Marshall, George C. -- Alone (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Marshall, George C. -- Groups of Three (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Marshall, George C. -- Groups of Two (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Marshall, George C. -- Large Groups and Crowds (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Marshall, George C. -- Wife and Family (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Marshall, Herbert -- Actor (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Marshall, Trudy -- Actress (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Martin -- A to J (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Martin -- K to Z (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Martin, Dean (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Martin, Glenn L. (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Joseph W., Jr., Representative (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Martin, Tony (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Martin, Tony -- And Wife (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Martz, Renee (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Marx -- Miscellaneous (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Mas (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Maschio, Johnny (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Mason -- Miscellaneous (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Mason, James -- Actor (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Massey, Ilona -- Actress (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Mat (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Mathias, Bob -- Tulare Athlete (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Matthews -- Miscellaneous (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Mature, Victor -- Actor (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Mauriello, Tami -- Boxer (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Max-Md (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Maxwell -- Miscellaneous (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Maxwell, Marilyn -- Actress (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - May -- Miscellaneous (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - May, Andrew J. (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Mayer -- Miscellaneous (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Mayo, Virginia -- Actress (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Mays, Willie (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - McA-McB (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - McAvoy, May -- Actress (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - McCaa-McCaq (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - McCallister, Lon (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - McCambridge, Mercedes (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - McCar-McCg (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - McCarran, Pat, Senator (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - McCarthy -- Miscellaneous (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - McCarthy, Joe -- Baseball (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - McCarthy, Joseph R. (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - McCh-McCl (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - McCloy, John J. (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Mccm-Mccq (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - McConnell -- Miscellaneous (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - McCormack -- Miscellaneous (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - McCormick, A-Z (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - McCormick, Bruce -- Golfer (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - McCormick, Dolly Ann (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - McCormick, Pat (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Mccr-Mccz (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - McCracken, Henry Ford (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - McCrea, Joel -- Actor (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - McCue -- Miscellaneous (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - McCullough -- Miscellaneous (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - McD (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - McDermott, Michael J. (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - McDonald, A-J (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - McDonald, Grace -- Actress (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - McDonald, K-Z (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - McDonald, Marie (Box 126, Folder 13 - 19)
    - McE (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - McEvoy -- Miscellaneous (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - McF (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - McFarland, Ernest, Senator (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - McGa-McGe (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - McGarry -- Miscellaneous (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - McGf-McGq (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - McGr-McG (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - McGrath -- Miscellaneous (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - McGuire, Dorothy -- Actress (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - McGuire, Katherine -- Actress (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - McGurk -- Miscellaneous (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - McHugh -- Miscellaneous (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - McHugh, Jimmie (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - McIntyre, J. Francis, Cardinal (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - McKa-McKd (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - McKay -- Miscellaneous (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - McKe-McKz (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - McKinney, Florine -- Actress (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - McL -- Miscellaneous (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - McLaglen, Victor -- Actor (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - McMillan -- Miscellaneous (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - McN-McZ (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - McNair -- Miscellaneous (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - McNear -- Miscellaneous (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - McNeil -- Miscellaneous (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - McNellis, Maggie (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - McNutt, Paul V. (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - McPhail, Larry (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - McPherson -- Miscellaneous (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - McPherson, Aimee Semple (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - McRae -- Miscellaneous (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Mea-Mee (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Mead, James M., Senator (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Mead, Meade -- Miscellaneous (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Medart, Mimi (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Medina -- Miscellaneous (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Mee -- Miscellaneous (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Mef-Mek (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Mel -- Miscellaneous (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Mem-Men (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Mem-Merk (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Mendl, Lady -- Elsie de Wolfe (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Mercer, Jacque -- Miss America of 1949 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Merkel, Una -- Actress (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Merl-Merz (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Merman, Ethel (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Merrill -- Miscellaneous (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Merritt -- Miscellaneous (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Mes-Met (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Messersmith -- Miscellaneous (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Mesta, Pearl (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Meu-Mez (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Meyer, John W. -- Howie Hughes' Little Friend (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Meyer, Meyers -- Miscellaneous (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Mia-Mic (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Michael -- Miscellaneous (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Michael, Gertrude -- Actress (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Mid-Mij (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Middlecojj, Cary -- Golfer (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Mik (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Mikhailovich, Draja (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Mila-Milk (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Mildmay, Lord Anthony Bingham (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Miles -- Miscellaneous (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Milford, Haven -- Marquess of (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Mill-Millz (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Milland, Ray -- Actor (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Miller -- Miscellaneous (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Miller, Ann -- Actress (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Millikin, Eugene, Senator (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Mills -- Miscellaneous (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Milm-Milz (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Mim-Min (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Mindszenty, Josef, Cardinal (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Minelli, Vincent -- And Wife (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Minton, Sherman (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Mio-Mit (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Miranda, Carmen -- Actress (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Mitchell -- Miscellaneous (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Mitchell, Cameron -- Mr. and Mrs. -- Johanna Mendel (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Mitchum, Robert -- Actor (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Miu-Miz (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Mize, Johnny -- Baseball (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Mj-Mog (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Moffett -- Miscellaneous (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Moh-Mons (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Molotov, Vyacheslav -- Russian Foreign Minister (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Monroe -- Miscellaneous (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Monroe, Marilyn -- With Joe DiMaggio, Jerry Giesler, Alone (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Mont-Monz (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Montalban, Ricardo (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Montez, Maria -- Actress (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery -- Miscellaneous (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Montgomery, Bernard L, General (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Montgomery, Douglas -- Actor (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Montgomery, George -- Actor (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Montgomery, Robert -- Actor (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Moo-Moq (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Moody -- Miscellaneous (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Mooney, Edward, Cardinal (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Moore -- Miscellaneous (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Moore, Archie (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Moore, Bryant, General (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Moore, Colleen -- Actress (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Constance -- Actress (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Moore, Grace -- Singer (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Moore, Terry (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Moore, Tom -- Actor (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Moorehead, Agnes (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Mora-Morel (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Moran -- Miscellaneous (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Moran, Dolores -- Actress (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Moran, Gertrude -- Tennis (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Moran, Lois -- Actress (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Moren-Morn (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Moreno, Rita -- Actress (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Morgan -- Miscellaneous (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Morgan, Dennis (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Morgan, Frank (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Morgan, Michele -- Actress (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Morley, Karen -- Actress (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Moro-Morz (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Morris -- Miscellaneous (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Morris, Chester -- And Wife (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Morris, Mary -- Actress (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Morris, Wayne -- And Wife (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Morrison -- Miscellaneous (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Morrow -- Miscellaneous (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Morse, Wayne -- Senator (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Mos (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Moss, A-Z (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Mossadegh, Mohammed (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Mossberg, Ann -- 1957 Rose Queen (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Mot-Moz (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Mountbatten, Louis -- Lord (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Mu-Mz (Box 135, Folder 10-20)
    - Mueller -- Miscellaneous (Box 135, Folder 21)
    - Munson, Ona -- Actress (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Murphy -- Miscellaneous (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Murphy, Audie (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Murphy, Frank -- Judge (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Murphy, George -- Actor (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Murphy, Mary (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Murphy, Thomas F. -- New York Police Commissioner (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Murray -- Miscellaneous (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Murray, Ken (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Murray, Mae -- Actress (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Murray, Philip -- C.I.O. (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Mussolini, Benito (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Myers -- Miscellaneous (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Myerson -- Miscellaneous (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - N-O
    - Naa-Nak (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Nader, George (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Nagel, Conrad -- And Wife (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Nagy, Ferenc (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Nal-Nap (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Naq-Naz (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Nash -- Miscellaneous (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - Nathan -- Miscellaneous (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - Nea-Nef (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Neal -- Miscellaneous (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Neal, Patricia -- Actress (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Neal, Tom (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Neg-Nen (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Nehru, Pandit (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Neill, Noel -- Actress (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Nelson -- Miscellaneous (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Nelson, Byron -- Golfer (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Nelson, Donald -- And Wife (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Nelson, Gene (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Nelson, Lori (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Nelson, Steve -- Communist (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Neo-Net (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Neu-Nev (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - New-Nez (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Newhouser -- Miscellaneous (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Newton -- Miscellaneous (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Newton, William Jesse (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Ney, Richard (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Nica-Nich (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Nichols -- Miscellaneous (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Nici-Nicz (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Nickel -- Miscellaneous (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Nid-Nih (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Nielsen, Nielson -- Miscellaneous (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Nii-Nil (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Niles, Robert (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Nim-Nj (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Nimitz, Chester W., Admiral (Box 139, Folder 15)
    - Niven -- Miscellaneous (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Niven, David -- And Wife (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Nixon -- Miscellaneous (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Nixon, Richard -- Alone (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Nixon, Richard -- Groups (Box 140, Folder 6-9)
    - Nixon, Richard -- Senator and Family (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Noa-Noq (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Nolan -- Miscellaneous (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - Noonan, Tommy -- Comedian (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Nor-Nou (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Norman -- Miscellaneous (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Norris -- Miscellaneous (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - North, A-Z (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - North, Michael (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Norton, A-Z (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Nourse -- Miscellaneous (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Nov-Noz (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Novak, A-Z (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Novak, Kim (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Novarro, Ramon -- Actor (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Novikov, Nicolai (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Np-Nz (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - O'Brien -- Miscellaneous (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - O'Brien, Edmund (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - O'Brien, Margaret -- Actress (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - O'Brien, Parry -- Shot Put (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - O'Brien, Pat -- Actor (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - O'Connell -- Miscellaneous (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - O'Connor -- Miscellaneous (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - O'Connor, Donald (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - O'Daniel -- Miscellaneous (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - O'Day -- Miscellaneous (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - O'Driscoll, Martha -- Actress (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - O'Dwyer -- Miscellaneous (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - O'Dwyer, William, Mayor (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - O'Hara, Maureen -- Actress (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - O'Keefe, Dennis -- Actor (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - O'Malley -- Miscellaneous (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - O'Neal -- Miscellaneous (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - O'Neil -- And O'Neill -- Miscellaneous (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - O'Niel -- Miscellaneous (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - O'Shea -- Miscellaneous (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - O'Shea, Michael (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - O'Sullivan, Maureen -- Actress (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Oa-Oj (Box 141, Folder 12-18)
    - Oakes -- Miscellaneous (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Oakie, Jack -- Actor (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Oberon, Merle -- Actress (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Odom -- Miscellaneous (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Oka-Op (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Oliver -- Miscellaneous (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Olivier, Lawrence -- Actor (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Olsen -- And Olson -- Miscellaneous (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Olson, Carl "Bobo" (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Ora-Orn (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Oriani, Ruth (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Oro-Orz (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Orr -- Miscellaneous (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Os (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Osmena, Sergio -- President of Philippines (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Ot-Ou (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Ov-Oz (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Overell, Louise -- Murder Trial Pictures -- October 1947 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Overell, Louise Beulah (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Owen -- Miscellaneous (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Owens -- Miscellaneous (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - P-Q
    - Paa-Pah (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Pace -- Miscellaneous (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Page -- Miscellaneous (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Page, Anita -- Actress (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Paget, Debra -- Actress (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Pai-Pak (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Paige, Janis -- Actress (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Paight, Carol Ann (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Pal-Pam (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Palmer -- Miscellaneous (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Pan-Paq (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Pandit -- Miscellaneous (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Panyushkin, Alexander S. (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Para-Parj (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Park-Parn (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Parker -- Miscellaneous (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Parker, Eleanor -- Actress (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Parker, Frank -- Tennis (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Parker, Jean -- Actress (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Parker, William H. -- Police Chief (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Parks -- Miscellaneous (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Parks, Larry (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Paro-Parr (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Paro-Paz (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Pars-Parz (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Parsons, Louella (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Pas-Pat (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Pasha -- Miscellaneous (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Paterson, Pat -- Actress (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Patrick -- Miscellaneous (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Patrick, Gail -- Actress (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Patten -- Patton -- Miscellaneous (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Patten, Luana -- Actress (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Patterson -- Miscellaneous (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Patterson, Floyd -- Heavyweight (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Patterson, Robert P. -- Secretary of War (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Patton, George S., Jr., General (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Patton, Mel -- Track (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Pauley, Edwin W. (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Payne -- Miscellaneous (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Payne, John -- Actor (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Payton, Barbara (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Pca-Pon (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Pea-Pec (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Pearl -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Pearson -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Peck -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Peck, Gregory -- Actor (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Ped (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Pee-Pem (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Peete, Louise -- Murderess (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Pen (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Pendleton, Nat (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Penney -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Pennington -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Peo-Peq (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Pep, Willie (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Pera-Perh (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Peri-Perz (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Perkins -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Peron -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Peron, Eva "Evita" (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Peron, Juan (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Perreau, Gigi -- Actress (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Perry -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Pershing, John J., General (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Pes-Petq (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - Peters -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Peters, Susan -- Actress (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Peterson -- Miscellaneous (Box 150, Folder 19)
    - Petiot, Marcel, Dr. -- French killer (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Petr-Petz (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Petrillo -- Miscellaneous (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Pettit, Paul (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Petty -- Miscellaneous (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Peu-Pf (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Ph-Pn (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Phillips -- Miscellaneous (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Pickford, Mary -- Actress (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Pidgeon, Walter -- Actor (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Pierce -- Miscellaneous (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Pinza, Ezio (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Pitts, Zazu -- Actress (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Pleven, Rene (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Pollard -- Miscellaneous (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Poo-Por (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Poolson, Norris (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Porter -- Miscellaneous (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Pos-Pq (Box 152, Folder 8)